Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - F
        - F-Dot - Telling me lies, SR-15030; F-Dot (Box 261)
          Catalog # D A-side Matrix # D+D 101 A
          D & D Records
          New York, New York
        - Fa Sho - The moocher, 1998; SR-15031; Fa Sho (Box 261)
          Catalog # U8P 1283; A-side Matrix # U8P-1283 A
          Universal Records
        - Fab 5 Freddy - Une sale histoire, 1982; SR-15032; Fab 5 Freddy, 1959- (Box 261)
          Catalog # AZ/0 156; A-side Matrix # MPO AZ 0 1756 A
          Disc' AZ International
          France
        - Fabe - Lettre au président, 1996; SR-15033; Fabe (Box 261)
          Annotated.
          Catalog # 578993 1; A-side Matrix # D FI-96-11 578993-1 A
          Unik Records
        - Fabe - Lentement mais surement (Remix et inédits), 1995; SR-15034; Fabe (Box 261)
          Catalog # 852 553-1; A-side Matrix # MPO 85255314
        - Fabolous - Can't deny it, 2001; SR-15035; Fabolous; Nate Dogg (Box 261)
          Catalog # ED-6295; A-side Matrix # STED-67231 A-1
          Elektra
        - Fabolous - Baby; Tit 4 tat (Dance mixes) (Disc one), 2005; SR-15036; Fabolous; Pharrell; Shorey, Mike (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15037. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 301759; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301754 A-1
          Atlantic
        - Fabolous - Baby; Tit 4 tat (Dance mixes) (Disc two), 2005; SR-15037; Fabolous; Pharrell; Shorey, Mike (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15036. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 301759; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301754 C-1
        - Fabolous - Ghetto Fabolous (Disc one), 2001; SR-15038; Fabolous; Ja Rule; Nate Dogg (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15039. Double album.
          Catalog # ED-6311; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6311-A
        - Fabolous - Ghetto Fabolous (Disc two), 2001; SR-15039; Fabolous; Ja Rule; Nate Dogg (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15038. Double album.
          Catalog # ED-6311; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6311-C
        - Fabrik, Tina - Non stop, 1982; SR-15040; Fabrik, Tina (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15041. Different discs.
          Catalog # PDS 430 DJ; A-side Matrix # PDS-430-A
          Prism
        - Fabrik, Tina - Non stop, 1982; SR-15041; Fabrik, Tina (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15040. Different discs.
          Catalog # PDS 430; A-side Matrix # PDS-430-A
        - Fabuloso - Radio active, 1994; SR-15042; Fabuloso (Box 261)
          Catalog # PE 0001; A-side Matrix # PE-0001-A
          Pandemonium Entertainment
        - Fabulous Billygoons - Rhapsody in flatuence, 1982; SR-15043; Fabulous Billygoons (Box 261)
          Catalog # MM 017; A-side Matrix # MM-017-A
          Modern Method Records
          Boston, Massachusetts
        - Fabulous Five Inc. - Jamaican woman, 1987; SR-15044; Fabulous Five Inc. (Box 261)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # SR-Jamaican Woman-A KK Mastering
          Stage Records
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Fabulous Five Inc. - You safe, 1984; SR-15045; Fabulous Five Inc. (Box 261)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # DSA 4053
        - Fabulous Pop Tarts - New York City beat, 1985; SR-15046; Fabulous Pop Tarts (Box 261)
          Catalog # BB 1202; A-side Matrix # BB-1202A-1A
          Baby Beck Records Inc.
        - Fabulous Thunderbirds - T-Bird rhythm, 1982; SR-15047; Fabulous Thunderbirds (Box 261)
          Catalog # CHR 1395; A-side Matrix # CHR-1395-AS-REI-PRC-C-2-1
          Chrysalis
          Los Angeles, California
        - Fabulous Thunderbirds - What's the word, 1980; SR-15048; Fabulous Thunderbirds (Box 261)
          Catalog # CHR 1287; A-side Matrix # CHR-1287-A S1
        - Face - Forever yours, 1991; SR-15049; Face (Box 261)
          Catalog # MIC 557; A-side Matrix # MIC MAC 557 A
          Micmac Records Inc.
        - Face to Face - Under the gun, 1984; SR-15050; Face to Face (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15051. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 49-05033; A-side Matrix # XSS-171812-1B
          Epic
        - Face to Face - Under the gun, 1984; SR-15051; Face to Face (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15050. 2 copies.
        - Fact or Fiction - Warning (Feel the rhythm), 1994; SR-15052; Fact or Fiction (Box 261)
          Catalog # Int-001; A-side Matrix # INT-001-A
          Intense Records
          Canada
        - Factor - Foolish, 1999; SR-15053; Factor (Box 261)
          Catalog # WR-251-1; A-side Matrix # WR-251-A
          Warlock Records
        - Factor E - Bring it, 2004; SR-15054; Factor E; Chadwick, Steve (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15055. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ADR-016; A-side Matrix # LB856MA ADR-016
          Afterdark Records
          Florida, United States
        - Factor E - Bring it, 2004; SR-15055; Factor E; Chadwick, Steve (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15054. 2 copies.
        - Factor E - Midwest coast breaks, 1999; SR-15056; Factor E (Box 261)
          Catalog # CTM9819-1; A-side Matrix # CTM 9819-1-A
          Contaminated Muzik
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Factual - For the song, 1984; SR-15057; Factual (Box 261)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # FACTION 03 A
          Faction Records
          Nashville, Tennessee
        - Faf Larage - Méchante soirée, 1999; SR-15058; Faf Larage (Box 261)
          Catalog # VVR5010056; A-side Matrix # FAF A POMPON TR VVR5010056
          V2
        - Faith No More - Another body murdered, 1993; SR-15059; Faith No More; Boo-Yaa T.R.I.B.E. (Box 261)
          Catalog # EAS 5449; A-side Matrix # XSS-5449-A-1A
          Immortal Records
        - Faith No More - We care a lot, 1987; SR-15060; Faith No More (Box 261)
          Catalog # LASHX 17; A-side Matrix # LASHX 17 A/1 420 R
          London American Recordings
          London, United Kingdom
        - Faithfull, Marianne - The blue millionaire, 1983; SR-15061; Faithfull, Marianne (Box 261)
          Catalog # DMD 627; A-side Matrix # STDM-44576-2
          Island Records
        - Faithless - Insomnia, 1997; SR-15062; Faithless (Box 261)
          Catalog # 07822-13333-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-13333-1-SA
          Arista
        - Faithless - Salva mea, 1996; SR-15063; Faithless (Box 261)
          Catalog # CHEK12.018; A-side Matrix # CHEK 12-018-A1
          Cheeky Records
        - Fake Fly Guys - Undercover lovers, 1985; SR-15064; Fake Fly Guys (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15065. 2 copies.
          Catalog # YRC-786-26; A-side Matrix # YRC-786-26-A
          York's Records
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Fake Fly Guys - Undercover lovers, 1985; SR-15065; Fake Fly Guys (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15064. 2 copies.
        - Falco - Rock me Amadeus (Salieri version), 1985; SR-15066; Falco (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15067. Different discs.
          Catalog # SP-12150; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012150 B ESI
          A&M Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Falco - Rock me Amadeus/Vienna calling, 1985; SR-15067; Falco (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15066. Different discs.
          Catalog # SP-12170; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012170-A-REI-ES
        - Falco - Vienna calling, 1985; SR-15068; Falco (Box 261)
          Catalog # SP-12182; A-side Matrix # AM SP 012182-A ES2
        - Falco - Nachtflug, 1992; SR-15069; Falco (Box 261)
          Catalog # 7 80322 1 A; A-side Matrix # 7803221-A2
          Electrola
          Germany
        - Falco - On the run (Auf der flucht), 1983; SR-15070; Falco (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15071. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-12063; A-side Matrix # AMSP 012063-A ES2
        - Falco - On the run (Auf der flucht), 1983; SR-15071; Falco (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15070. 2 copies.
        - Falco - Wiener blut, 1988; SR-15072; Falco (Box 261)
          Catalog # 1-25690; A-side Matrix # 1-25690-A-SH1
          Sire
        - Falco - Emotional, 1987; SR-15073; Falco (Box 261)
          Catalog # 0-20666; A-side Matrix # 0-20666-A-SH2
        - Falco - Data de groove, 1991; SR-15074; Falco (Box 261)
          Catalog # V-76358; A-side Matrix # V-76358-A
          American Sound Records
        - Falco - The sound of musik, 1986; SR-15075; Falco (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15076. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20529; A-side Matrix # 0-20529-A-SH1
          The Netherlands
        - Falco - The sound of musik, 1986; SR-15076; Falco (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15075. 2 copies.
        - Falco - Rock me Amadeus/Vienna calling, 1985; SR-15077; Falco (Box 261)
          Different jacket
        - Falco - Junge roemer, 1984; SR-15078; Falco (Box 261)
          Catalog # SP-4993; A-side Matrix # SP-4993 A RCA-1
        - Falco - Der kommissar, 1982; SR-15079; Falco (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15080. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-12053; A-side Matrix # AM SP 012053-A PI
        - Falco - Der kommissar, 1982; SR-15080; Falco (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15079. 2 copies.
        - Falconer, Roderick - Victory in rock city, 1977; SR-15081; Falconer, Roderick (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15082. Different discs.
          Catalog # UA-LA777-G; A-side Matrix # UALA 777-1
          United Artists Records
        - Falconer, Roderick - Rock City, 1977; SR-15082; Falconer, Roderick (Box 261)
          In same jacket as # SR-15081. Different discs.
          Catalog # UA-DW1077; A-side Matrix # UADW1077
        - Faline, Tony - Breakdown '99, 2000; SR-15083; Faline, Tony; Mike & Charlie (Box 261)
          Catalog # UN 016; A-side Matrix # UNION-016-A
          Union Records
        - Faline, Tony - One funky fresh DJ; Get funky, 2000; SR-15084; Faline, Tony; Huda Hudia (Box 261)
          Catalog # US-001; A-side Matrix # UNISCOPE001ARE
          UniScope
          Tampa, Florida
        - Faline, Tony - Beat it, 1999; SR-15085; Faline, Tony (Box 261)
          Catalog # Un008; A-side Matrix # union08
          Sarasota, Florida
        - Fall - Cruiser's creek, 1985; SR-15086; Fall (Box 261)
          Catalog # BEG 150T; A-side Matrix # BEG-150T-AA
          Beggars Banquet
          United Kingdom
        - Fall - Slates, 1981; SR-15087; Fall (Box 261)
          Catalog # TRADE THREE 10; A-side Matrix # TRADE THREE-10A
          Rough Trade
          Berkeley, California
        - Fam-Lay - Fresh n drivin'; Git busy, 2004; SR-15088; Fam-Lay; Pharrell (Box 262)
          Catalog # DEFR 16093-1; A-side Matrix # B0002954-11A
          Star Trak Entertainment
        - Fam-Lee - Runs in the Fam-Lee, 1992; SR-15089; Fam-Lee (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15090. Different discs.
          Catalog # C 47367; A-side Matrix # AL-47367-1A
          JMJ Records
        - Fam-Lee - Runs in the Fam-Lee, 1991; SR-15090; Fam-Lee (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15089. Different discs.
          Catalog # CAS 4461; A-side Matrix # XSS-04461-A-1A
        - Family - The screams of passion, 1985; SR-15091; Family (Box 262)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2336; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-2336-SH1
          Warner Bros. Records
          Burbank, California
        - Family - The screams of passion, 1985; SR-15092; Family (Box 262)
          Catalog # 0-20360; A-side Matrix # 0-20360-A-SH1
        - Family Brown - Imaginary world, 1977; SR-15093; Family Brown (Box 262)
          Catalog # UA-LA828-G; A-side Matrix # UA-LA-828-1
        - Family Brown - I'm gonna getcha, 1984; SR-15094; Family Brown (Box 262)
          Catalog # BZ1102; A-side Matrix # BZ-1102-A
          Buzz Records
          United States
        - Family Dream - Rescue me, 1987; SR-15095; Family Dream (Box 262)
          Catalog # 67816/67814; A-side Matrix # 4585MGA-67814-15B
          Motown
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Family Stand - You don't have to worry, 1997; SR-15096; Family Stand (Box 262)
          Catalog # ED-6037; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6037A-1
          EastWest Records
        - Family Stand - Ghetto heaven, 1990; SR-15097; Family Stand (Box 262)
          Catalog # PR 3154; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-58118-58116-58119-1
        - Family Stand - Ghetto heaven, 1990; SR-15098; Family Stand (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15099. Different discs.
          Catalog # 0-86238; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-58118-58119-1
        - Family Stand - Ghetto heaven, 1990; SR-15099; Family Stand (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15098. Different discs.
        - Fanatik - Kubonics (Instrumentals) (Disc one), 2000; SR-15100; Fanatik (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15101. Double album.
          Catalog # HTK015; A-side Matrix # S-45530 OASIS DISC MAST HTK-015-1 (A)
          Heratik Productions
          Oakland, California
        - Fanatik - Kubonics (Instrumentals) (Disc two), 2000; SR-15101; Fanatik (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15100. Double album.
          Catalog # HTK015; A-side Matrix # S-45532 OASIS DISC MASTEM HTK-015-1 C
        - Fania All Stars - Guasasa, 1989; SR-15102; Fania All Stars (Box 262)
          Catalog # JM-660; A-side Matrix # JM-660-A
          Fania Records
          Miami, Florida
        - Fantastic Four - I got to have your love, 1977; SR-15103; Fantastic Four (Box 262)
          Catalog # ST-DSKO-33978-PR; A-side Matrix # ST-DSKO-33978-B
          Westbound Records
        - Fantistica - From ear to ear, 1971; SR-15104; Fantistica (Box 262)
          Catalog # SG-0014; A-side Matrix # SG0013A
          Ghetto Records
        - Fantasy - Live the life I love, 1983; SR-15105; Fantasy (Box 262)
          Catalog # QUS 037; A-side Matrix # QUS-037-A
          Quality Records
          Scarborough, Ontario
        - Fantasy Three - Summer, 1984; SR-15106; Fantasy Three (Box 262)
          Catalog # C.C.L. 301A; A-side Matrix # CCL-301-A
          C.C.L. Records Inc.
        - Farel, Robert - Perdu sous l'equateur, 1986; SR-15107; Farel, Robert (Box 262)
          Catalog # 883 787-1; A-side Matrix # 2228837871 // 1 380 POLYGRAM
          Barclay
        - Farley Funkin Keith - Funkin with the drums, 1985; SR-15108; Farley Funkin Keith (Box 262)
          Catalog # FFK846-6273; A-side Matrix # PRL85 19AX
          House Records
        - Farley "Jackmaster" Funk - Love can't turn around, 1986; SR-15109; Farley "Jackmaster" Funk; Jessie Saunders (Box 262)
          Catalog # 886 075-1; A-side Matrix # 261 886075 1 // 1 380 POLYGRAM
          London Records
        - Farrakhan, Louis - Heed the call ya'll (Disc one), 1980; SR-15110; Farrakhan, Louis; Farrakhan, Minister Louis (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15111. Double album.
          Catalog # SCR 101 A; A-side Matrix # FCR-101 A
          Final Call Records
        - Farrakhan, Louis - Heed the call ya'll (Disc two), 1980; SR-15111; Farrakhan, Louis; Farrakhan, Minister Louis (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15110. Double album.
          Catalog # SCR 101 C; A-side Matrix # FCR-101 C
        - Farrakhan, Louis - Let us unite, 1984; SR-15112; Farrakhan, Louis (Box 262)
          Catalog # 10903; A-side Matrix # 20184-A
          A.V.C. Records
        - Farrakhan, Louis - Our time has come (Disc one), 1984; SR-15113; Farrakhan, Louis; Farrakhan, Minister Louis (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15114. Double album.
          Catalog # 30901; A-side Matrix # 30901-A
        - Farrakhan, Louis - Our time has come (Disc two), 1984; SR-15114; Farrakhan, Louis; Farrakhan, Minister Louis (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15113. Double album.
          Catalog # 30901; A-side Matrix # 30901-C
        - Farrari - Simon says dance, 1983; SR-15115; Farrari (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15116. Different discs.
          Catalog # SH-451-A; A-side Matrix # VID-252A
          Sugar Hill Records
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Farrari - Simon says dance, 1983; SR-15116; Farrari (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15115. Different discs. Annotated.
          Catalog # SH-451-A-X; A-side Matrix # VID-252AXX
        - Farrell, Joe - Night dancing, 1978; SR-15117; Farrell, Joe (Box 262)
          Catalog # BSK 3225; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3225-LW2
        - Farrow, Cee - Should I love you, 1983; SR-15118; Farrow, Cee (Box 262)
          Catalog # XR 95508; A-side Matrix # S-10525 RE-XR 95508-A
          Rocshire Records
          Universal City, California
        - Fashek, Majek - So long, 1992; SR-15119; Fashek, Majek (Box 262)
          Catalog # 0-96180; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-61963-61964 DMM-1
          Interscope Records
        - Fashiøn - Streetplayer-mechanik, 1982; SR-15120; Fashiøn (Box 262)
          Catalog # ARIST 12456; A-side Matrix # ARISTA 12456 A//1 420 H
        - Fashiøn - Move on, 1982; SR-15121; Fashiøn (Box 262)
          Catalog # CP-719; A-side Matrix # CP-719-A
        - Fast Lane - Young ladies, 1984; SR-15122; Fast Lane (Box 262)
          Catalog # S.U.I. 101; A-side Matrix # SUI-101-A
          Straight Up
        - Fat Boys - Disco 3, 1984; SR-15123; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15124. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SUD 024 A; A-side Matrix # SUD-024-A
          Sutra Records
        - Fat Boys - Disco 3, 1984; SR-15124; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15123. 2 copies.
        - Fat Boys - Hard core reggae, 1985; SR-15125; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          Catalog # SUD 038; A-side Matrix # SUD-038-A
        - Fat Boys - Fat boys, 1984; SR-15126; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15127. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SUS 1015; A-side Matrix # SUS-1015-A
        - Fat Boys - Fat boys, 1984; SR-15127; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          In same jacket as # SR-15126. 2 copies.
        - Fat Boys - Crushin', 1987; SR-15128; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          Catalog # 422 831 948-1; A-side Matrix # 422-831-948-1-AS-HRM
          Tin Pan Apple
        - Fat Boys - Lie-Z, 1989; SR-15129; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          Catalog # 889 747-1; A-side Matrix #
        - Fat Boys - All you can eat, 1985; SR-15130; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2399; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2399-SH1
        - Fat Boys - Falling in love, 1987; SR-15131; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          Catalog # 885 766-1; A-side Matrix # 885-766-1-BS-ES
        - Fat Boys - Falling in love, 1987; SR-15132; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          Catalog # PRO-516-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-516-1-BS-ES
        - Fat Boys - In the house; Breakdown, 1986; SR-15133; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          Catalog # SUD 049; A-side Matrix # SUD 049 A
        - Fat Boys - Jail house rap, 1984; SR-15134; Fat Boys (Box 262)
          Catalog # SUD 027; A-side Matrix # SUD-027-a
        - Fat Joe - Success (DJ Premier remix), 1995; SR-15135; Fat Joe (Box 262)
          Catalog # RPROLP 0410; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0410-A
          Relativity
          Jamaica, New York
        - Fat Joe - So much more, 2005; SR-15136; Fat Joe (Box 262)
          Catalog # PR 301709; A-side Matrix # STPR-301709-A1